Back up!
Keep going!
Who is it that you sense nearby weather?
Are you saying that Jolyne's
the one who's near the hospital?
Or do you mean the priest is
the person that's already here?
Actually, I can sense
three people, Anastasia.
Jolene is one of them.
The priest is here, too.
But there is somebody else.
We gotta find them.
But where are they?
Could they be inside
one of these buildings?
Excuse me, ladies. Welcome
aboard. Unfortunately,
this plane is expected
to lose control and crash
into the ground at approximately
21.33 on July Saudi, 2005.
Hey, hold on.
What do you think you're doing, Jolene?
You're not planning on
opening that door, are you?
I wasn't able to find
the exit on the ceiling.
So the fastest way to end this is to find
the stand user and attack him directly.
Hermes, hold on tight to my rope again.
And strap yourself in somewhere.
And you, flight attendant lady,
switch the settings on this door
so that I can open it manually.
Yo, hang on.
It ain't exactly a good idea to open
the door when the plane's still moving,
you know?
The air pressure would...
Huh?
Nah, never mind!
Go for it!
Use the air pressure to slam
into those motherfuckers!
Mayday, mayday!
Looks like we just got hit by a damn MiG!
I've lost all control!
I guess finishing them will
be easier than I thought.
Hey, who are you?
Anyway, I think the back of
the plane took a serious hit.
Can you go check out
how bad the damage is?
What the hell?
Oh shit!
Joey!
Stone Ocean!
This is Officer McCoy here.
We just arrived at the scene.
Not sure what happened.
I can't tell how deep it is from the
surface, but there's a large hole.
As I told you, Jolene Kujo's
skills were sharpened in prison.
She already anticipated
what could happen in
the event that her initial
attack was a failure.
Clearly, this is why she
got out of the airplane.
She was waiting for the police to arrive,
so that they would use their radio,
giving her a chance to grab it.
Now she can contact her Allies
depending on frequency range that
radio can be used to call cell phones
as well shut the Fuck up already
enough does it look like I'm
losing here huh answer me father
poochie I'm Still winning this damn
battle aren't I destiny is mine?
Let's go.
Thank you so much for watching.
In the end of the day,
it's the end of the day of my life.
I didn't have any cash, so it was
only going to be for a few days,
but as I was looking for a
place to spend the night,
a pair of spiked shoes
came falling from the sky.
They were baseball spikes, and
they had a real nice smell.
I looked up to see if someone
threw them from the building above,
but they looked so new.
The shoe size was 28
and a half centimeters.
Though they were way too big for me,
I liked the clacking sound the spikes
made when I walked down the street,
so I decided to keep them on for a while.
It wasn't long until some
cops came and arrested me.
This hearing today is not a formal trial.
We just want to ask some questions.
Understood.
Did you steal those
shoes you were wearing?
Turns out,
those spikes were signed by the
famous baseball player Ichiro
and donated to a facility for
children with disabilities.
If you sold them to a collector, they
would have gone as high as ten grand.
So everybody wanted to
get their hands on them.
Like a dumb kid, I told the truth.
They came falling out of the sky.
You should be ashamed of yourself!
How dare you steal from
children less fortunate!
You need to be straightened out!
Go spend some time in the
juvenile detention facility!
The judge found me
guilty on circumstantial
evidence and sentenced me
to six months in juvie.
And even my parents agreed to it.
Four months later, the
actual culprit confessed.
Since Ichiro's spikes were so famous,
the thief knew they'd be found and threw
them in an air vent to be rid of them.
And somehow, they ended up
outside of the building.
By the time it was discovered
that I was wrongly condemned,
I was already crippled in mind and body,
to the point where I was too
weak to even walk straight.
One day, I fell into a
random hole in the fields.
In the moment,
all I could think about was breaking
my fall by extending my hand out.
And that's when I saw a knife in a
plastic bag that had been buried there.
It went right through my hand.
What do you think you're
doing causing me trouble, kid?
I was hiding that knife
there for a reason, you know.
The next day, a guy three years
older than me kicked my ass.
He was a gangster's little
bitch that did his dirty work.
Even though my hand was
treated by a doctor,
two weeks later my wound
was still expelling pus?
and worms even started crawling out of it.
After that, I nearly
died from a high fever.
Since then, I've tried to live
a bitter life of solitude,
keeping away from the public
eye as much as possible.
Then one day, when I was taken
to piss by some garbage cans,
the wall started to
crumble and revealed the
skeletal remains of a
woman who died years ago.
And now, after all this time,
the reason why my life has been so utterly
fucked up is finally crystal clear to me.
It's my ability.
Netherworld!
But still,
just because I can control my power now,
am I really supposed to
be grateful to Father
Pucci for helping me
realize my full potential?
Hell no.
The blood that's been running through
my veins all along is Dio's, my father.
So, Priest, do you honestly believe
you're that important to all of this?
Do you not think that I would throw
your ass onto that plane as well?
I haven't even failed yet!
I haven't done anything wrong!
He's just like that old bitch of a
judge who only values her own opinion.
I'm really starting to lose my
patience with this so-called holy man.
I am the one who's invincible here.
Anything is possible if I use Netherworld!
Why is he the only one?
On the new moon, maybe it should
be me who comes out on top.
What if I'm the one who acquires Dio's
power instead, and not that damn priest?
I have every right to it.
After all, I am Dio's son.
It's Weather Forecast's memory disk.
Well, maybe this can be used
to put things in my favor.
The only one who gets to
attain heaven should be me.
Joey!
Come on, Emporio!
Pick up the phone!
Now, Emporio! Hey, Mr. Pilot!
What kind of jet fighter is this?
And how the hell do I get out of here?
There's got to be some way to break
loose, even if I'm still sitting down!
I've seen it in lots of movies!
Hurry the fuck up and tell me how!
The seat has a lever you
can pull to eject yourself,
but in my case, I never
got the chance to escape.
My jet hit the ground before
I was able to pull it.
That is the truth.
That's why nobody's gonna be
getting off this aircraft.
It's already too late to pull
the ejection lever in time.
Jolene, is something wrong?
What are you doing calling so soon?
Listen, Emporio!
No!
Right now we're in a big
hole in the hospital floor,
and Hermes is riding on a
plane that's gonna crash!
I'm in a fighter jet
that's also about to crash!
Find a way for us to get out of here!
Huh?
Father Poochie, do we need
Jolene's body intact after this?
They weren't able to
retrieve all of the jet
fighter pilot's remains
after the jet crashed.
You see, he was blown to bits.
Hold on, just calm down, Jolene.
I don't understand what
you're saying at all.
I'll head back to the hospital right away.
No, don't come here, Emporio.
We're trapped in an
incident from the past.
This crash is already predetermined.
The only way to survive it is to escape
from the cockpit, but I have no idea how.
It's no use.
We ain't gonna make it.
We're out of time.
There's less than a minute remaining,
and the fighter jet Jolene's
on is gonna crash even sooner.
Huh?
Wait, the jet fighter didn't.
You're absolutely right.
It didn't blow up, Emporio.
Even though I crashed the jet
into the plane, it didn't explode.
There's no way it would.
If it crashes into the ground in the past,
then it won't blow up until that happens.
Until then, no matter what you do,
neither of the planes will explode.
Yo, Jolene. I'm back.
Emporio, help me figure out
what to do next. Let's see.
In a miraculous turn of events six
years ago on flight 2882 to Dallas,
two of the passengers survived somehow.
I'm looking the story up right
now on my ghost computer.
You need to get to their seats!
Escaping from that airplane is impossible!
But if this is really an event
that occurred in the past,
you should be able to survive
if you sit in those seats!
Hurry, Emporio!
Find out which seats they are!
Well, that's Jolene Cujo for you.
She always figures out a
way to create her own path.
Now then, do you think you're capable
of getting the job done, huh, Versus?
Shut your mouth!
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Found it, Jolene.
An old newspaper recorded
the seats that the
survivors were sitting in
at the time of the crash.
It looks like they're an economy class.
Seats 51D and 51F.
They're all the way in the back,
and you should know they weren't lying
about the time of the crash being 2133.
It's the truth!
Run, Julie, run!
The enemy's inside the plane with us!
He's trying to get to
those seats before we do!
He wants to destroy them so we can't sit!
32 seconds until impact.
It's not that big of a deal.
Just prevent them from sitting.
Doing so will bring about their end.
Hermes, we need to protect the seats!
If we can save those seats and make it
out of the plane crash in one piece,
we should be able to
confront the stand user!
We've got to survive, so we can beat
the living shit out of the user himself!
Hmm, I couldn't destroy the
seats, but you'll never sit there.
You have just 21 more seconds.
Jolene, I repeat, you can sit in
seats 51D and 51F, but only those two.
Do not try to sit in any other seat!
According to the records,
all of the other seats were blown away
when the plane crashed and exploded!
Luckily,
those two seats endured because the impact
created a quantum vacuum around them,
so they're safe!
Once again, sit down, make
sure you fasten your seatbelts!
And protect yourselves with your
stands, otherwise you won't make it!
Huh? Move it!
I'm gonna take this seat from you!
Hey, what are you doing to me? Shut up!
Get out of my way!
You guys aren't even actually real!
You're just records of who survived!
You aren't humans or
some kind of lost souls!
The actual survivors aren't
living their life right now!
So stay point!
Jolene, it's time!
Fasten your seat back -
Whoa, hey kid! Move it!
Why the hell are you
sitting in those seats?
Wait a sec, Hermes!
Wait what's going on here?
Who are you two?
I don't think I'm in my room anymore.
But where am I?
It's time to change my bandages then
I have to take medicine after my nap.
Did you two rats fall from the ceiling?
Nah that can't be.
This isn't good. They're not.
Memories of passengers and we're
definitely not hallucinating.
Hey uh when is the nurse gonna be here?
We're actually real kids.
That son of a bitch!
Versus must have grabbed
these kids from the
hospital and pushed them
down into the hole above us.
Oh there's no longer a need
to destroy those seats.
Jolene Kujo don't forget
to fasten your seat belt.
Now go ahead and toss those brats.
aside and take your seats.
In that way, the two of you will
survive the crash and your sorry lives
will be spared.
But by the time you climb out of
the wreckage of the crashed plane,
you'll be left with the crushing
weight of guilt on your conscience.
The guilt of sacrificing innocent
children so you can live another day.
Then you would have to
come face me head on,
carrying that guilt as a
constant reminder of your choice.
Would anyone in a position like
that have the fight Left in them to
keep going my stand netherworld
isn't the strongest when it comes to
fighting abilities but with your
guilty conscience and broken spirit
it's more than powerful enough to
snuff out your life hey you there
jolene what are you guys doing
over there tell me what's happening
who's that person you're talking to
damn it yo the plane's rocking back
and forth jolene we have to grab
the kids and sit two to a seat we
can't we'll all die that way there's
There's only space for one person!
Besides, we have three
kids to think about!
Excuse me, ma 'am, are these your seats?
Well, I'm not exactly very good at
standing up by myself, but I'm sorry.
We'll move out of your
way, so please sit down.
The time's come.
Two seconds till impact.
One second.
And now.
July!
It appears that you have defeated them.
Good work, Versus.
But you sent three
children onto that plane.
That was one extra kid.
Do you not feel even a little guilty?
For what?
It wasn't my fault that happened.
It was all because Jolene made contact
with her friend over the radio.
It was them who found the
survivor's seat numbers.
And also, remember who it
is I did all of this for.
You, Father Poochie.
Hey, Versus, look there.
That sticker it belongs to Hermes
It's on the old man who survived
the fact that he is still
with us means that no matter
what Happens the survivors won't
die and sing us how that's
Hermes's sticker using its special
ability She duplicated the
survivors and hid the child inside.
Where'd Ermes go?
And...
Jolene's gone too!
Where are they?
Where is Ermes?
Ermes!
She hid herself in the body
of the female survivor!
Shit! Er... Ermes!
But that means Jolene is dead for sure!
There's no way Jolene could have
found a way to escape that explosion.
If I were in your position,
I wouldn't allow such simple-minded
thoughts to cloud my judgment.
Asshole.
Exactly whose side are you on?
Jolene unraveled as much of her
body as she could into threads.
Then she hid inside of my body so she could
protect herself against the collision.
Good freaking grief.
Jolene Kujo wasn't consumed by
guilt like you were expecting.
Instead, she's coming at you angrier than
ever with a righteous sense of justice.
What will you do now, Versus?
Another world!
You're done excavating
incidents from the past.
I won't let you dig up the
ground's memories anymore.
And now we finally got
you backed into a corner.
You lose, poochie.
Do you want me to take
care of this holy bastard?
Aren't we going to finish this
worthless ass off together?
How unfortunate, Versus.
It seems as though you
have lost this battle.
By successfully bringing
herself closer to me,
Jolene proved her destiny
is stronger than yours.
Go get him, Jolene!
Time to finish that fucking
asshole off already!
Weather forecast!
What the hell was that?
What's going on here?
Come on, Jolene, kill his
ass before he gets away!
When did you steal it?
Was it just now when you got
blown away by Jolene's punch?
you must return it.
Hand it to me quickly.
You cannot comprehend the
forces with which you're
meddling in.
Don't know about you,
but I'm not dying here.
Sorry, Father Pucci.
Definitely not
when I've just gained control
over my very own abilities.
Until now, I've spent my life in
shame and unable to stand up straight.
There's no way I'm
gonna die when I finally
understand why I was born into this world.
You don't understand a
single solitary thing.
It is imperative that That man
does not retrieve his memory,
at least not for another three days.
I don't care, I'm not dying like this.
I still have a right to live
a happy life too, don't I?
What's that supposed to mean?
What the hell are you guys talking about?
Jolene, forget about all that crazy
shit and just killed the fucker.
It's pointless to even try.
You two won't be able to kill me anymore.
He's going to get his memory back.
I know this because I just
read the contents of his disc.
And when he does regain his memories, your
so-called friend will not be your ally.
Memory?
Do you mean Weather Forecast?
Was it his disc that you just threw?
Getting his memory stolen and
being thrown in prison aren't the
only misfortunes that poor Weather
Forecast has had to deal with.
He doesn't even remember how to use
his stand to its fullest potential.
Unable to access the
forbidden power which his
brother Poochie thought he
had sealed away forever!
Because Weather happens to be
the priest's biological brother.
Could it be that Rikyo was actually
telling us the truth before?
Weather forecast and the priest!
I see,
so you had already used your netherworld
to read the secrets
held in his memory disk.
Versus!
You insignificant piece
of refuse and scum!
Don't think that you can
invade upon the fortress
that Lord Danny have carefully cultivated!
Do you finally remember everything
now, Pucci? Look up there. It's coming.
Those rainbows.
Look at them all!
It's heavy forecast!
The Devil's Rainbow!
Weather, what's wrong?
Which way is Jolene?
And why are you keeled over?
Weather, what's your deal?
What are you doing?
What was that for?
Yo, answer me!
I was sitting in that seat, you know!
Get your disgusting hands
off me, you asshole!
I'll kill you!
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
with hope of some
place other than here.
Although you think I smile
inside and all the while,
I'm wondering about my destiny!
I'm thinking
about all
the things I'd like to do?
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming far
away from today.
you Thank you.